Come on.
Let's toast.
For our advancement to the knockout stage.
Cheers.
Come on, hurry up.
Take a seat.
Dig in.
The pot is already boiling.
By the way,
I need
take a picture for Xu Anbo.
He's too busy to even
answer video calls.
I need to show him
this feast
and make him jealous.
Come on.
You all get in the picture.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Today,
I must have a drink
with my big hero alone.
Thank you, coach.
Thank you, everyone.
Sit, sit, sit.
You persisted with an injury.
This is completely different
from the first time I met you.
This is what you call "climb higher and higher".
Come on.
I'll give you a big rib as a reward.
Thank you, coach.
Step by step, higher and higher.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Wishing you all rise to greater heights!
Thank you!
Today,
it's not just a celebration.
I also have some good news
to share with everyone.
I've been confirmed for regularization.
The process has already started.
Congratulations, Coach!
Congratulations!
The reason I could stay
is because of
your efforts.
If the school
didn't see the results of our basketball team,
I would have been eliminated long ago.
So,
I especially want to thank these two.
Thank you for your efforts.
As a reward,
each of you can have a chicken leg.
Thank you, coach.
Here.
Coach,
don't say that.
Fu Binyan and I
have learned a lot
from you.
Yeah.
Without our coach,
the former MVP,
we wouldn't have
made it this far.
Honestly,
after I retired,
I was lost for a long time,
feeling really down.
Truth is, coming to Yibei
wasn't my idea at all.
My mom signed me up behind my back.
What?
Well then,
we should
kowtow to her.
No need for that.
But
she was so prescient.
She has a keen eye for talent.
I was very reluctant at first
and even argued with my mom.
You all saw it.
At first,
I was just goofing off.
But then I met you guys.
You guys lit a fire under me,
and I pulled myself together.
Auntie, you didn't know
Yibei would have
talented players like us,
especially me, did you?
Not at all.
Just eat.
Come on.
Eat and listen.
By the way,
there's one more thing.
Actually,
I was one of the first members
of the Yibei Basketball Club.
Really?
Surprised?
I actually
founded
the Yibei Middle School
Basketball Club with my teammates.
My mom sent me back
to help me rediscover myself
from scratch.
Seeing you all now
reminds me of my younger days.
So,
next,
let's raise our glasses, everyone.
I'll give it my all
to lead you to keep pushing forward
and see greater heights and further horizons.
Come on.
Cheers!
Yibei Basketball Team!
Go, go, go!
Turn off the gas!
It's off.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Why are you all at home?
You cooked again?
Well,
didn't you say
you're going on a road trip?
Such a rare opportunity,
you just give up like that?
We're not going.
Fine.
We two,
seeing your performance
on the court today,
Brother Lin and I
were deeply moved.
We just felt
that you seemed
to have suddenly grown up.
The two of us
don't want to fall behind you.
So we decided
to also grow up,
so we can continue to be your support.
The first step in your growth
is to blow up the kitchen.
Look at you,
saying this at such a sentimental moment.
It's like this.
Back then,
when we played Cooking Dash,
we didn't break up.
I thought
if I can play this game,
then when it comes to cooking,
have some talent.
Who knew...
Who knew our
talent is playing games.
Cooking is really...
Alright.
Then,
I support your decision.
However,
safety must come first.
Can you do that?
Yes, ma'am.
Yuan,
you also have to promise me
one thing.
No matter where you are in the future,
and under what circumstances,
you must ensure that
you don't get hurt again.
Can you do that?
Yes, ma'am.
Then let's
grow up together.
Yes.
Congratulations, Haoyu,
on winning the competition
and returning triumphantly.
Congratulations!
Haoyu,
you guys did an amazing job today.
Thank you.
Dad,
you look so cool today.
Haoyu,
you are my pride.
Dad,
what's wrong with your voice?
It's my first time watching you play.
You're amazing.
I got so excited,
kept shouting,
now I can't even speak.
Your dad
is our
cheerleader captain today.
Dad.
Dad, slow down.
Dad is so happy.
Limited edition.
I've been eyeing it for a long time.
Awesome.
Thank you, Dad.
Haoyu,
keep it up!
Okay.
Thank you, Aunt Su.
Keep it up!
Thank you.
Thank you, Jiang Yi.
I made you Champion noodles.
Exclusive for Haoyu, let's go.
Okay.
Let's go.
You're back.
Here.
A gift.
Take a look.
This is...
This is all the data analysis
you did after you returned to the basketball club.
I organized, printed,
and designed it.
I know
maybe these analyses
are not professional enough,
but
this is my son's effort.
It's also the proof
of your real effort.
I want to keep it.
Thank you.
Mom
Although I can't play on the court,
I'm still not bad.
Really?
Of course.
You are my pride.
Come on.
Take a look.
Mom.
Don't worry.
I'm fine at home by myself.
I'll go to bed early.
You too.
Surprise!
Mom.
Why are you back?
Didn't you say you'd stay at Fang He's tonight?
You've made it to the knockout tournament.
How could I not come back
on such an important day?
I brought you
Fang He's most famous pastries.
Do you want some?
Yes!
Are you happy?
Why are you back so late?
Dad.
It's already 10 p.m.
We won the game.
Coach Su treated us to dinner.
He told Mom about it.
Dinner?
So you were having dinner
until now, right?
Afterwards, we went
to the beach for a while,
and played some basketball.
Your study area
is such a mess.
You should clean it up.
And your clothes are all over the place.
You weren't like this before.
How are you supposed to study
in this kind of environment?
Are you getting
bad influence
from your friends?
Gu Chenyang,
you weren't like this before.
If you keep this up...
Enough, enough.
How are you going to
study hard like this?
You should pick your battles.
He just won the game today.
Don't nag him.
So what if he won the game?
If he's wrong, he should be corrected.
Does correction also need to be timed?
Right, right, right.
That's why I'm correcting you in time.
Why are you correcting me?
What do I need correcting for?
You've worked hard today.
He's worked hard?
What's he worked hard for?
Cut the crap.
I'm going out.
Don't push me.
I'm not only going to push you,
I'm also going to hit you.
Gu,
do you know
you look like
a feudal father
in an old romance drama
in old romance dramas.
The kind that leaves children
with a shadow of the original family.
Really?
I was so amiable just now.
I, I, I...
I treated him as a friend
to communicate.
I...
Did I?
A little bit.
No, I...
I really want to treat him
as a friend.
Right?
If you treat him as a friend,
then friends
also have times of quarreling.
Besides,
if you are friends,
shouldn't you
treat each other sincerely
and not deceive each other?
If you like basketball, just tell me.
Right?
If you have a talent in this area,
I will definitely support you.
But you don't need to lie to me.
You don't need to hide it from me.
Once you hide it from me,
I'll be angry.
Don't be angry.
Calm down.
Was I really
so
condescending?
A bit overbearing.
My heart
is wasted on you.
Your heart
is all mine.
It's not wasted.
Do you remember
back in college,
you were known as a top student.
Your study and life were all planned.
Everything was arranged in order,
and executed meticulously.
That's right.
But later,
you broke the rules
just to have dinner and hang out
with me.
It had to be broken.
Maybe
for Yang,
it's the same.
Maybe.
What do you mean by "maybe"?
You're funny, Xiao Yun.
How can you compare yourself to a ball?
You...
What are you talking about?
Right.
I shouldn't have used that metaphor.
Mr. Gu is right.
I understand your thoughts,
but I also understand Yang.
No matter how you advise him now,
he can't possibly understand your vision
and foresight
at this age.
He might have to
take some detours.
You need to be mentally prepared for that.
I am prepared.
I understand.
Children
need to be tempered.
Right?
He has to
learn the hard way.
He has to take the winding road.
When he was in primary school,
he had a charity sale.
It's okay.
You can
take all sorts of detours.
But this
switch in sports specialty
is a big deal.
Right?
I...
I can't just ignore it.
Xiao Yun,
at home,
you be the good guy.
It's
okay.
I...
Father.
I can be the bad guy.
Father's love is like a mountain.
Right?
Your Five Fingers Mountain.
I'm just gonna crush it.
Before the Buddha
crushes the Monkey King,
before Buddha
put him under the Five Fingers Mountain?
Not in a fatherly way.
Not in a fatherly way?
Then
how do you do it?
Then...
Then you make him my dad?
Yangyang,
I want to discuss something with you.
Is that okay, Yang?
You...
Well...
You're getting goosebumps.
No way.
I'm getting goosebumps too.
I can't do this.
My father's dignity is gone.
You...
Practice a bit.
Make it look natural.
I can't.
This is...
No way.
I can't say that.
Gu Tingjun,
you
can do anything.
I believe in you.
You're the best.
Fine.
Let's practice.
Practice, practice, practice.
Yang.
No, no.
What's going on with you two?
A sighing contest?
It's in the chat.
Take a look.
Yudong Middle School
has a whole
basketball training center,
with two training gyms,
a dedicated fitness area,
and equipment
I can't even pronounce.
They also have
a full coaching staff,
including fitness coaches,
analysts,
and therapists.
Are you kidding?
Why not just go play
in the NBA?
How can we compare to them?
We're just a makeshift team.
No wonder they can beat
the Sports Academy.
Everyone has different equipment.
You just realized?
Yudong's equipment
is the best in our province.
It's also a key school in the province.
It's good for study.
In recent years,
relying on the signboard of college entrance examination enrollment rate,
it has recruited many
good students in junior high school.
But they only look at ability,
not character.
That's why they produced
someone like Guo Rui.
Do you want to be friends with him?
I heard that
Yudong and the Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education
are both managed in a military manner.
And the competition within the team is fierce.
In order to be the starter,
the players are more like opponents than teammates.
The pressure is huge.
This is the price of excellence.
Rules,
efficiency,
results
matter most.
Wait,
doesn't that sound
just like Gu Chenyang?
Don't twist my words.
I didn't.
That's just how it is.
You're pretty chill now,
That's good.
Is it because you've been
with these friends too long,
you've been led astray?
Gu Chenyang,
you weren't like this before.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
You're fine, just eat.
It's too high in calories.
Forget about that!
Just eat.
Gu Chenyang,
you've been
lost in thought.
What's up?
Nothing.
I'm thinking about
our next opponent,
Experimental High School No. 5.
They weren't mentioned in the profile.
The editor said
the next one
will be released in a couple of days.
Ours hasn't been released either.
But this school
is indeed unheard of before.
We need to study it well.
Dad.
Hello, uncle.
Yang.
Daddy.
Dad.
What's wrong?
I...
Dad.
What's going on
with you today?
I...
It's nothing.
I just
came to see you today.
and see how you're doing at school.
I had a chat
with your coach.
He's a nice guy.
He even showed me
around the training hall.
By the way,
he specifically mentioned that
you're great and creative,
and you often discuss tactics
with him.
It seems that
I underestimated you.
That's because
of the study habits you taught me.
That's how I can do all this.
It seems that
I'm still
useful to you.
Of course.
Dad,
do you agree with me playing tennis?
I told you that day.
I don't care
what sport you choose.
Whether it's tennis
or basketball,
I will support you.
I just feel
that you've been hiding it from me.
You don't treat me as your own.
This makes me uncomfortable.
I can't accept it.
I was wrong.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid that you...
Enough.
Let it go.
Okay?
I'm not here
to lecture you.
Since you like basketball
and are talented in it,
I'll fully support you.
Then we are
still best partners.
OK.
Don't be so happy.
Except for basketball,
what about other aspects?
I won't fall behind in my study.
I'll plan my time well.
I'll report to you as usual every week.
Don't say report,
it's exchange.
Exchange between friends.
Right.
Friends.
Exchange.
Right.
It's a deal.